Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
That Osman didn't only take your soul...
... he also took your wisdom!
You have forgotten that
you can not trick Balgay!
I will take this new soul from you...
... so that it won't kill your true self!
You will be Kongar again!
You will call Balgay "Father" again!
You will be my best soldier...
... who lunges into the
death fearlessly again.
Why didn't you say that Zöhre
took the poison from that man...
who came to the Tent, Hazal Hatun?
Degenerate. And he says he's a doctor.
- It's not easy to see, Osman!
- What if you were late?
What if something went wrong?
Why did you wait for the meeting?
I wanted to be sure!
Are you interrogating me,
instead of thanking me?
It's not an interrogation,
aunt. It's inquiry.
Osman wants to see who's behind this.
Maybe there wasn't someone behind this.
Maybe she made the poison herself.
I don't think so.
That poison is nothing we know of.
It's potent. Its effects come out later.
She gives the poison to the animal. But it
becomes deadly after the animal is cooked.
What kind of malice is that?
Even the devil wouldn't think of this!
The devil walks amongst us, uncle.
His medicines are lies.
You think that man who we thought was
a Muslim was someone else, Osman?
He is someone else, Hazal Hatun.
So he gave the poison,
instead of medicine.
Who is this snake that came to my home?
We will know about him,
I sent my soldiers after him.
Who do you suspect? Who is behind this?
Sofia.
Isn't that centipede in Constantine?
The poison is Hemlock. It is an ancient,
deadly Greek poison with hemlock in it.
No one could've thought
about this but her.
First, we capture him.
Then we'll see what he has to say.
Konur, it's the castle
is there, after his hill.
That treacherous doctor
will leave his home soon.
We need to be careful, Boran.
Will be.
That's Sugutay.
Stop, brother. Put it down.
They are going to the castle, Boran.
They are going to the castle.
Now we know how Sofia was brave enough
to poison us in the wedding, brother.
Now we know.
How did they survive the poison?
How?
They killed Zöhre Hatun, she
must have exposed herself.
I did my work, Princess Sofia.
Damn your legacy, Osman!
Princess Sofia, Mongol
Commander Sugutay is here.
Osman will track you, hide your
tracks, go to the Nicaea, hurry!
Commander Sugutay.
How good to see you.
If I know you were coming...
I would've given a feast in your honor.
This way.
Here. We will talk here, Sofia.
Under the sky, like a Mongol.
I am so hungry.
Bring the food.
Your tents of rock...
... and your glamour is tiring me, Sofia.
Glamour gives friends trust,
and enemies fear.
Nonsense.
We Mongols...
... believe that we take the soul of the
animal whose heart we eat.
I think you ate chicken hearts.
Seeing that you trapped yourself here.
I came here to give you courage. Take it.
Horse heart. Eat it so that
your eyes are opened.
And your soul is filled with courage.
You will need it.
I like my meat bloody.
I'm listening.
Tell me why I'll need courage.
Geyhatu...
... has returned because of Baydu.
He gave me the mission
to end that devil Osman.
It's not easy to end Osman, Sugutay.
Don't you trust me, woman?
As much as I trust Geyhatu.
What do you want from me?
It's enough for me to make Osman
and his Alps leave the Tent.
It's my job to drive Osman mad
and make him leave the Tent.
And you, what have you got?
I have...
... a betrayal that's going to take
Osman to the spirit realm.
Kill him!
End of the line, dog!
You will die!
I am innocent.
Nice dagger.
Sharp.
But sharp daggers cut their owners first.
If you lie to us, we will
cut your tongue out.
Forgive me!
Zöhre Hatun asked me
to give her the poison.
How could I know she
would do such a thing?
Didn't I tell you I will cut
your tongue out if you lie?
Princess Sofia!
She made me do it.
She threatened me with
my kids! Forgive me.
What were you doing in the castle then?
I told Sofia that I did what I could...
... and to leave my family alone.
These news won't be enough
for us to forgive you.
We need more.
Commander Subutay.
He came to visit Sofia.
They'll move together from now on.
You've tried to turn our feast into
funeral and our Tent into graveyard.
Know that in our custom, we don't
tolerate treachery.
You will kill Osman with this dagger,
Salvador.
By slaughtering soldiers, he left
behind corpses as much as Mount Olympus.
What will we succeed with this dagger,
princess?
This dagger...
...has such a poison on it that...
...a little scar on his body
will be enough to kill him painfully.
With this scar, he'll first feel the
poisoned cold death...
...at the back of his neck.
What about pain?
Is there any pain?
Talk me about that.
Pain.
Pain moves slowly until it covers
his entire body.
When he vomits, his life will
flash before his eyes.
He'll question his loyalty and
treachery.
In order to deceive Osman, you've
changed your religion.
You're the person suitable for this job.
Die!
Burçin.
Is that the thing you're
looking for?
Oh, my daughter.
Oh, my Burçin.
Your wound is
still fresh.
Don't tire yourself.
My wound is not on my body.
It's on my heart.
I'll heal the wound on your heart.
I'll heal.
Be careful about the wound on your body.
That's enough.
I don't have the power to stand in front
of you because of what I've done.
But, you forgave me.
Oh, my Burçin.
Nobody is sinless in this world.
Don't think about that.
Don't.
Also, do you know what is inside of this
chest? Look.
Come here.
Come.
Bismillahirrahmanirahim. (in the name of Allah,
the compassionate, the merciful)
Allah. Allah is my witness.
I didn't preach my Aybars anything
except the remark of Allah.
When he was a little boy, he started
to read it.
He insisted on being mollah.
Then, he didn't.
He just didn't.
Oh, my Burçin.
Praise be!
My Burçin.
My Aybars grow up with this flag.
He saw all dreams in which
this flag was waving.
All dreams.
My Burçin.
This dagger is the first dagger that
I attached to his waistline.
He first killed a Mongol unbeliever
with this dagger.
With this dagger.
Now, all of these belong to Sıddık.
But these are the
belongings of Aybars.
And also who is Sıddık?
Sıddık is the second son which Allah
gave to me, my Burçin.
He is the rose that blossoms in winter
and the snow that falls in summer.
Now, he will come to the Tent to kiss my
hand.
When he comes, I'll introduce you to him.
I will.
Did you feel the cold breath of death
on the back of your head, Salvador?
The death is reuniting with
our Allah for us.
Before you reunite with your God...
...I'll reunite you with Osman whom
you trust faithfully, Salvador.
I liked you.
Princess Sofia.
You're a funny woman.
Now.
Go to osman and say that...
Did you make him speak?
Fortunately, my bey.
What did that dog say?
I wasn't mistaken, my bey. He works for Sofia.
He got out of the castle.
But there's an another problem.
You were right about your doubts, my bey.
Subutay is collaborating with Sofia.
We saw his soldiers while
going to that castle.
After Alişar died, he found a new
ally.
Subutay should have gone to
Geyhatu with that greed.
As he didn't, he is planning
something new.
We need to take precautions in the
Tent without giving it out.
We can't know what they will do.
You speak right, brother.
Thanks.
What this red devil is doing in here?
I know her.
Her words are effective.
Did she poison you as well?
Anger is no use for any of us.
Balgay.
Either you'll kill each other or
you'll kill Osman together.
Geyhatu came back because of Baydu threat.
He ordered me to kill Osman.
I know Osman.
We've both set off and
gone to the war with him.
He has willpower like an iron.
This won't be easy.
I saw him as well.
Poor Turkmen has scared you.
The last thing that Sofia had done
will drive him crazy.
Salvador was a soldier that
Osman placed next to me.
I poisoned and sent him to
Osman as a wedding gift.
You are such a devil that...
...you will spoil his wedding.
I thought this woman was a coward.
But it seems that Yannis made her
brave while she was young.
Now, we need a move to trap Osman who
went crazy.
That's the easiest one.
The blonde berserker who will trap
Osman is staying there.
Now, by possessing his soul I will
make him a wild bird.
Did your magic work, the great shaman?
Did you capture his soul?
Wake up him then.
Wake up wild bird.
Kongar.
My son.
Father.
What happened to me?
The mean man named
Osman has stolen your soul.
The great shaman wanted it
back...
...and took it.
Are you ready for listening my orders,
my son?
Sıddık.
Who is that? Sıddık?
Help us.
Hurry! Come on!
Sıddık.
Brother. Who did it to you?
Sofia.
She told me that she went back to take his
father revenge.
Son.
Sıddık. My son, son...
Sıddık, my son.
Don't leave me.
Look. I am here.
I am here. Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Stay strong, son.
Stay strong, Sıddık!
- Father...
- Yes, son. Tell me.
Tell me.
Kongar...
My blonde berserker.
My angel of death,
bright like the sun...
You'll go to the Kayı Tent.
You'll tell them that you're compromised
and bring Osman to Kartal beech.
Then you'll take your revenge from
that fool who stole your soul.
As you order, father.
Osman is a traitor.
He will die.
Kongar will kill him.
The bait is on its way.
While Kongar brings Osman...
... we'll prepare for the ambush.
Both Osman and Kayı Tent will end.
You promised! Sıddık, you promised!
Stay with me. Stay with me!
Hold on!
Hold on, Sıddık! Hold on, son!
G--
Give your blessings, father.
No, no.
[Kalima Shahadah]
No...
You promised...
I'll be your Aybars, you said...
I won't go anywhere,
I'll stay with you, you said.
Thank Allah for giving me such a fate.
What if he died as an infidel?
What if he was from the cruel ones?
Thank my Allah...
... that he died as a believer.
My Allah...
... accept him to Hz. Hamza's lodge.
- Amen.
Accept him to Hz. Hamza's lodge.
Amen.
My Osman!
This is the second son Sofia took from me.
The second son, my Osman.
There isn't enough space in this world
for me and Sofia, Bamsı Bey.
Start preparing! After burying our martyr,
we'll do what's necessary!
As you order, my Bey!
We're witnesses, dear Allah!
He came as a Catalon,
he went as a Turk!
- We're witnesses, dear Allah!
He came as a Christian,
he went as a Muslim!
- We're witnesses, dear Allah!
He was lost,
then he found the way.
- We're witnesses, dear Allah!
We're witnesses, dear Allah.
We are!
We're witnesses, my Bamsı Bey!
The entire world will be witnesses
once we take our revenge!
My Osman...
We'll bury him next to my Aybars.
So that they can be together
in the afterlife.
So that they can be together.
Don't worry.
Come on.
- Easy.
- Let's go.
My Aybars is with me.
We'll bury him next to my Aybars.
Let's go, Osman.
My father, Osman,
everyone should pray for you.
That traitor Zöhre was about
to kill the whole Tent.
Back then, I knew how to get her when
she tricked them to exile you, but...
... there is a time for everything, son.
Patience is hard,
but its fruits are sweet. Remember that.
You're right, mother. I've witnessed
the misery you've gone through.
You grieved for me and also my father.
But as you've said,
there is a time for everything.
The time has come.
But I can't do it alone.
You will help.
Anything you want, mother.
Gündüz Bey has no power in the Tent.
Osman can be regarded as the Tent's Bey.
He'll be the Bey after his father dies.
You...
But you are...
... the nephew of
Muzafferidun Yavlak Hasan.
You're his pride.
Remember.
Always remember why he sent you here.
The power and might of the Kayıs are
the keys to these lands.
Those who hold those keys control
the borders.
What about Osman?
What'll we do about him?
Osman isn't our issue.
Geyhatu will deal with him.
The problem comes after Osman.
Kayıs have to survive and recover in you
and your father's hands.
That's what your uncle wants.
Understood?
Understood, mother.
You should stay close to Osman.
You'll gain his trust.
If necessary, you'll sacrifice your
life for him. I shouldn't say that.
Or you will pretend.
I waited for this day
in my brother's Tent.
With patience, endeavour...
I waited with great effort!
This is the day.
Without taking
my revenge for all those years...
... without taking control
of these borders...
... I won't let this go.
As long as you listen to my words, son.
They've hastily married.
They've sacrificed many, many animals.
They've ruined a young bride.
They ruined her.
Brother!
Why are you staying away, brother?
Don't go, brother!
Brother! Stay!
Brother!
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
[in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.]
You see...
Your wisdom can't be questioned,
Abdurrahman Gazi.
Our Allah who shows us the light of day...
... takes our children to
his side one by one.
As you see now,
both of them lay side by side.
May Allah put them
in the same place, brother.
I hope we have the same testimony as them.
Amen, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Amen.
Göktuğ?
Göktuğ!
Are you okay, brother?
Who did this to you?
Who did this to you, Göktuğ?
Balgay found everything out.
I've been compromised.
I hardly got away.
If I stay with him,
I can only die alone.
From now on, there's only death
for Balgay, brother!
Not to you! Only to Balgay!
Where is that degenerate?
He established his base at Kartal beech.
He's working with Sofia and Subutay.
He sold you out.
My Osman!
We should go and take their lives!
We knew about Sofia
and Subutay's alliance.
Since Balgay wants to beef with us...
... then he deserves an earlier death.
Brother. You and Abdurrahman Gazi
should stay at the Tent.
Keep your eyes wide open.
Çetin and Ayaz should be with you.
Don't worry, brother.
Our enemies are working together
to destroy us.
They want the Turkishness to end.
They don't want any Muslim left.
But they don't know that...
A place with a Turkish gravestone...
... is our homeland.
This is the day we'll teach this to them.
- Allahu Akbar!
Come, brother.
Come, Göktuğ.
Göktuğ! Are you okay?
My dear brother!
I'll attack from the front with my Nökers.
The lucky ones will be crushed
by our horses.
The others will taste
our naphthalized arrows.
Some will try to escape from here.
Your soldiers will hold the Tent's exit.
No one will get out of there alive.
I'll be commanding my soldiers,
Commander Subutay.
I waited a long time to hear them
beg for their lives.
But we shouldn't underestimate Kayı Tent.
I know many people who tried to kill them
but lost their own lives.
Not a simple death...
I'll give them hell.
What are you doing here, Bahadır?
While the horses of my Tent are running
for battle, I can't sit and wait, Osman Bey.
What do you wish from me?
I know that you're angry towards me.
A lot happened because of my carelessness.
But I'm regretful, Osman Bey.
If you allow me,
I'd like to be by your side.
Our path is harsh.
It's not for those whose lives are sweet.
Osman Bey, won't you accept it
for my brother Batur's sake?
If my life is sweet, I'll sacrifice it
for your cause!
Come, then.
Selcan Hatun! Bala Hatun! Come!
What happened, daughter?
- Aygül isn't here!
- What do you mean?
She isn't here! She went to her tent
to sleep.
I went to look and she wasn't there.
I've searched the whole tent.
- Oh no!
- I asked everyone.
No one saw her.
What will we do, Selcan Hatun?
Relax, daughter. We'll find her.
Did you inform Hazal Hatun?
I couldn't find her.
Do you think they left together?
I don't think so. Hazal Hatun was near
the pavilion. I just saw her.
Whatever it is! We'll find Aygül. She's
out of her mind. May Allah protect her!
We need to find her before it gets dark.
Alps!
Aygül isn't here! Inform Dündar Bey.
We'll look for her. go!
- Okay, Selcan Hatun.
Osman Bey!
We'll walk from here.
They're on the other side of the hill.
Göktuğ...
You don't look okay.
- You should stay here.
- Osman Bey...
Allow me to be with you while you
get that dog Balgay.
Don't deny me my revenge.
Bamsı Bey. We'll go from here.
You surround the flank.
We will, my Osman.
For my brother Batur, Osman Bey!
Valiants! For my sons!
For all our martyrs!
Let's go.
Let's go, valiants!
What should we do?
Should we seperate?
Mother, I know where she is heading to.
What's in your mind? Speak.
She is with the one who she is
crazy about.
Come on.
Hide! Move!
-Hazal...
''Hazal Hatun seems pretty dignified''
Yes, she is so dignified.
Humans hide their real pattern inside.
Indeed, indeed.
Why did she come here after all
these years?
Only for Bahadır?
I don't think so.
She is using an iron hand in a
velvet glove...
...I'd say that she is planning something.
- You are right, son.
''Don't you worry. I'll keep an eye
on her.''
Where is she going to with such hurry?
Bala, my girl.
I hope you are right.
You go and find Aygül.
And I'll go after her.
Let's see what she is after.
- Be careful, mother.
- Don't worry.
Come on.
Two dogs cAme together...
... and talk about our death.
It's time for revenge, Osman Bey.
It's time to wash the blood with blood.
It's time to take revenge from Balgay for
all the things he had done to us.
Come then, Osman.
With the name of Allah!
Balgay!
My Bey, it is a trap.
Osman...
For you and your warriors...
...I summoned Erlik Khan's sons.
Baybadur the Stonehand...
...Karaş, God of Darkness...
...Kerey Khan, Yabaş Khan, Badış Khan...
...Kömür Khan, Karaş Khan...
They all gathered...
...for the bottles of blood...
...that I will offer to them.
Nine holy sons of Erlik Khan...
...with the feast of souls I
offer you...
...surround all around!
I offer Osman to your father...
...accept it.
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ...
Konur...
What have they done to you, Göktuğ?
Valiants, brave men...
Now, this is the place.
Come on now. Come on, come on.
I got my son's soul back, Osman.
You can never take a Mongol's soul.
We came from Allah and we
will go to Allah.
Göktuğ...
Break your chains, brother!
For your brother!
For your mother and father whom
they killed, turn back to Allah.
Göktuğ...
Göktuğ!
Göktuğ's soul is with blue skies
and dark clouds.
The one standing here is Kongar...
...my son, Kongar.
Erlik Khan, I offer you Osman's soul.
Göktuğ!
Now you say...
...why did Hazal Hatun return
to the Tent?
After all this time, which wind
led her here?
You should know that it wasn't a
wind that brought me here.
It is fire. The fire of children in
my heart.
We will see, Hazal Hatun.
Is is the fire of children...
...or some other plans...
...we will see.
Remember your testimony with
your pure heart, Göktuğ.
Huh, brother?
May dark souls take Osman's soul
to Erlik Khan.
Now we are face to face, Osman.
Cerkutay...
I heard that Salvador is gone, as well.
How many children will you
sacrifice for Osman Bey?
Did you think that...
...we will be out of children to sacrifice
for homeland?
Stupid man.
Cerkutay.
Are you high?
Take your guard, Cerkutay.
If a father doesn't behead a red
handed heathen...
...how can he face Allah in
the other world.
Boran, Bahadır, warriors!
Osman is in danger.
Come on, come on.
Come with me.
Aygül Hatun!
Aygül, my girl!
Aygül Hatun.
Aygül, my Aygül!
- Aygül Hatun!
- My girl, where are you?
- Aygül!
My Aygül...
Aygül Hatun!
Uncle, calm down.
We will find Aygül.
How will we find her, my nephew?
This is a giant forest.
Who knows where she went.
We will find her.
Selcan aunt is after her.
Maybe they will find her before us.
Don't be like this. Don't worry.
We will find her. May Allah help us.
- We will.
- Inshallah, my nephew. Inshallah.
Aygül!
My Allah, help my girl.
Don't let me face this pain.
I can't bear it.
Protect my daughter.
Aygül Hatun!
Aygül! My girl!
Where are you?
My child, my girl,
where are you?
What are you after, Hazal Hatun?
What are you doing?
Who is this?
I won't wait for you!
You will come first and wait for me!
- Did you understand?
- Yes, Hazal Hatun.
Now...
I'm listening.
Tell me.
What news did you bring?
I brought Muzafferidun Yavlak
Hasan's news.
The things I'll tell you are
rather important.
You told me to stay alive
until we got even.
This is where we get even, Osman.
You've sharpened your sword
with treachery.
You've armoured your dead with unrest.
Now, I'll be the end of you.
Nökers! Don't interfere.
I'll make the most of killing Osman.
Kill him! Don't let him get away!
I'm here, Osman!
My Osman!
Osman! I'm here, Osman!
I'm here, my Osman!
Balgay! Balgay is running away, my Osman!
Let's go!
Göktuğ! Göktuğ killed his brother.
Konur is injured, Bamsı Bey.
I'll go, you take care of him!
Konur! Konur! Son!
Konur! Konur, don't!
Open your eyes, son!
My heart can't stand more, son!
It can't stand more! Son!
Open your eyes!
Konur! Don't!
Son! Open your eyes!
Bamsı Bey!
You fell from grace!
What did you do!?
Don't, Bamsı Bey.
Don't kill my brother.
Bamsı Bey, enough! Enough.
Balgay took him from us. Don't do it.
All of you will die like dogs.
Like dogs...
They've raced,
they've danced...
The feast was beautiful.
You used to dance so nicely.
I wish you came.
I waited for you. But you didn't come.
- Aygül.
- My brother came. He called me.
I told him about the feast and the games.
How nice of you! But you
left before telling us, Aygül.
We got worried.
Don't worry about me.
My brother is always with me.
He'll protect me.
Don't worry.
Come on, Aygül.
We should return to our Tent.
Will you take good care of Osman Bey?
I will, Aygül. Don't worry.
Let's go.
Also my baby...
I promised you.
Of course I will.
Let's go.
- Aygül Hatun!
- Aygül! Daughter!
- Aygül!
My daughter!
My daughter! My Aygül!
Stop!
Don't eat the food!
This traitor poisoned the food!
Eat it.
Coward!
Daughter?
I'll take your life
if you try to take ours!
Mother!
My daughter.
Okay, okay.
Please stop.
Come on, come on my daughter, let's go
back to our tribe.
Mother!
My Bey, this is my bequest.
Don't let Balgay take Göktuğ.
Don't worry. I will make Göktuğ my Alp.
Okay, don't tire yourself up.
- Dumrul.
- My Bey.
Cauterize right now.
Göktuğ.
They destroyed your sanity.
They owned your soul.
Göktuğ.
Wake up.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
(in the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.)
Don't you see your brother's condition?
Göktuğ, how could you do that?
Thank your brother that I gave my word
to him.
Or else...
Osman.
I took what I want, Balgay.
But...
I will still keep my promise.
When you gather the commanders under you,
I join your war and help you kill Geyhatu.
However, if your soldiers act like Böke,
I will kill you by myself.
You owe me now.
Valiants don't forget heir debt.
I don't forget anything.
Don't die until the day of our war.
You trampled my honor.
You took my son from me.
My skin was thick, you couldn't bore.
My weapon was blunt, you couldn't handle.
I fought a thousand times,
I resurrected a thousand times.
I have fought against you once, I have been
defeated a thousand times by you, Osman.
No one can defeat the glorious Balgay.
Balgay is still glorious Balgay.
However, his glory is in Osman's hand.
Where are you going, Balgay?
I will take my glory back from Osman.
Ghengis Khan's Nökers (soldiers)!
Show your glory!
May your anger take them down!
No Kayı will be left alive!
Make a mountain with the heads you take,
make a stream with the blood you shed!
Tents, tribes, barns...
Burn it all down!
Today, Erlik Han will be full of blood!
Erlik Han will be full of blood!
Erlik Han! Erlik Han!
Hey death!
Where is your victory?
Hey death, where is your thorn?
The messiah resurrected, you are defeated.
The messiah resurrected, devils died.
The messiah resurrected, angels delighted.
The messiah resurrected, the vita
has risen.
The messiah resurrected, everybody
resurrected.
Because the messiah became the first
dead.
Godspeed to him...
-for ever. Amen!
-Amen!
I don't want any Turk alive!
Or I will kill you all!
For my father, the head monk Yannis...
For a world without Turks...
Long live princess Sofia!
Destroy!
Destroy them!
Don't show mercy!
I am here! Where are you!
The cowards hided in their tents!
I don't want any alive Turk!
Find them all!
Kill them all! To the tents!
This is a trap!
That's a trap!
Trap!
Run Run!
Attack!
Attack them!
Come on, Hatuns!
Don't forget, son...
...it's the most important discipline
of Islam's very old history.
When Muslims fall apart, unbelievers rise.
Your duty is to get yourself together.
Kayı Tent...
...is the archery hill of
Muslims in Bithynia.
If we leave there...
...unbelievers will double their cruelty.
Now, protect your Tent..
...and action.
So that Muslims rise and
unbelievers fall apart.
Osman...
So, you ran away from Balgay.
Göktuğ! How could you
kill your brother?
Do you think I only killed that dog?
I destroyed your whole Tent.
- What are you saying?
- Commander Subutay...
...will raid your Tent with Sofia.
They'll kill everyone.
You're late, Osman.
You're late.
That's my gift for you
before you die.
When you arrive at your Tent...
...everyone will be dead.
They'll raid our Tent, Osman!
They set a trap to our minds and anger...
...with Sıddık and Göktuğ.
We are far away from the Tent, Osman Bey.
How will we reach there?
As soon as possible, Bahadır.
Till we have our own graves.
We don't know what we'll face in the Tent.
Dumrul.
Look after these two.
Take care of Konur.
- Look after him.
- Your command, my Bey.
We'll go to the Tent immediately.
Shahada road is waiting for us!
Allah will help us...
...and Hızır will be our comrade on
this road.
Come on!
- Give me your blessings.
- I will.
I thought you were bad...
Look at me, Hazal.
Don't try my patience.
Now tell me what your problem is or...
...I'll make you regret the day you
were born and make you say it.
I got some news from my brother.
Subutay will raid the Tent.
You saved the Tent, Hazal Hatun.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to my brother.
These dogs would kill all of us if he
didn't tell me. Come on!
You can't stop a tiger, Osman.
Traitors' fate is...
...the grasp of...
...fearless, Subutay.
I'll kill you.
Are you looking for us, Sofia?
Come here.
Allah is eternal!
Attack!
Fight, valiants!
Kill all of them!
Allahu Akbar!
You're late, Balgay.
They got news about raid
and took precautions.
Osman arrived just in time.
I swear that...
...I won't ever stop, Osman.
I'll take back my son Kongar...
...from you.
I'll torture you to dead, Osman.
I'll torture you!
Come on, valiants! Today
is the Shahada day!
Kill them all!
I came with a Mongol anger!
You'll drown in Turk's revenge, Subutay.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries